Cu 10 ani în urmă
Wh-What is this?
Where am I?
Yes! A success!
The summoning is a success!
Heroes!
God has sent us heroes to save Distinia!
What?!
You are visitors to our
realm from another world.
The god-sent saviors of our nation!
Heroes! Heroes! Heroes!
Wh-What?
What are you idiots raving about?!
I never agreed to that!
Huh?
Heroes or not, we just got dropped
here with no idea what's going on!
Don't try to dump your own problems on us!
Hero, what is your name?
Setsu. My name is Setsu.
Setsu-san...
Episodul 9
Invocat pentru prima oară într-o altă lume
Setsu-san, how can you stay so calm?
After being dropped into this
messed-up world out of the blue...
This world has monsters and
demon lords and stuff, right?
If that's the case, we have to be strong,
regardless of what we end up doing.
I can't think like that.
Going to war in this foreign world...
I don't want to do that. I'm scared.
Yeah, but complaining changes nothing,
since we're already here.
But it's a war!
Having to risk our lives fighting enemies
we don't even know in this unknown land...
That's just wrong.
I know, but that doesn't justify
us doing nothing right now.
Yeah, but...
Since we're in the same boat here,
let's do our best to survive.
As long as we stay alive,
I'm sure things will work out.
Setsu-san...
Hey, Toma.
Huh?
Let's stop this war. The two of us.
Stop the war?
You're right.
Killing and getting killed by strangers
in this unknown land is wrong.
That's impossible.
There's nothing we can do
to stop an ongoing war.
Besides, I'm not strong like you, Setsu-san.
We're the chosen heroes, right?
How do you know what's
possible before we try?
We're the only allies we've got,
since we come from the same place.
In a way, we're brothers
from the same hometown.
So I'll protect you.
Setsu-san...
You can stop calling me "-san."
That's a promise, Setsu.
Yeah, it's a promise.
Are you really leaving, Setsu?
Yeah, I've gotten pretty strong.
If I want to stop the war,
I need to see this world with my own eyes.
Sorry... I'm still scared.
But...
But I'll get stronger.
Strong enough to fight and stop the war.
So, when the time comes...
Yeah, let's meet again once we've
both become heroes for real.
That's a promise.
That's a promise, Setsu.
Toma the Hero!
Your valor and accomplishments in battle,
your unflinching loyalty to the
nation, and your endless effort
have earned you the title of knight
and the honorific "Silver Hero"!
I accept this overwhelming
honor with gratitude.
You finally did it, Toma-sama!
A knight! You're finally a knight!
Soon, you will be an officer... no, a general,
and be able to lead this whole nation!
It's way too early for that, guys.
Setsu, I've gotten one step
closer to our promise.
I'll get stronger,
both personally and politically.
Then I can end this war.
Of course, Toma-sama.
I'll forge on to fulfill my dream.
Are you all willing to die for me?
Of course!
Our lives for Toma-sama!
Let's go, everyone!
To my ideal world!
Yes, sir!
Heave, ho!
Charge!
Don't let anyone escape!
If you let one escape,
we'll be the next ones to die!
No!
It's the Silver Devil!
What's this place?
W-We surrender!
Please, spare our lives—
No. This war needs to end.
Toma-sama, the temple has been cleared out.
Good work.
Reorganize the survivors.
We'll head out immediately.
Yes, sir.
The weak, the pitiful,
the ones who should not exist.
Who's there?
I can see inside your heart.
Your envy, your despair, your hatred.
Yeah, whatever.
I see your deepest secret, your true desire.
My true desire?
Who are you to tell me what my desires are?
I will grant them to you.
I will give you the power and the destiny.
My desire is...
Now, grasp me in your hand...
To fulfill your desire.
Come...
Of course, Toma-sama.
I'll forge on to fulfill my dream.
Are you all willing to die for me?
Of course!
Our lives for Toma-sama!
More enemies...
I have to keep fighting...
My promise...
My dream...
Toma-sama!
An urgent message from the royal capital!
A truce has been called in the name of peace.
All forces are to immediately
cease hostilities!
Peace?
The delegation of leaders
who will sign the treaty
will be passing through this area soon.
We are ordered to protect their safety.
This magic power...
Can you really?
It's really good!
You can say that, but...
You don't trust me?
Not until we taste it.
Who eats squid?
Why is Setsu there?
Next is the unveiling ceremony for the
monument to memorialize this peace.
Representing the end of this long war
and our hope for everlasting
peace... here it is!
Setsu the Hero! Setsu the Hero!
Cheers!
It's a festival!
Cheers to peace!
The war is over!
What's wrong? You look sulky.
Setsu...
You're amazing, Setsu.
You really ended the war.
I just went places and did as I pleased.
I didn't do anything special.
Really? I could never do the same.
Come on. You're much more important now, too.
That's awesome.
Our promise...
My promise with you... This was the only way...
Setsu-sama!
Please hurry up!
We can't start this party
without the main guest!
Oh, sorry! Be right there!
So yeah, gotta go.
I'm glad you're well, Toma.
S-Setsu!
Um, uh...
You know...
I worked hard in this world, too,
and went places myself.
And I was told at a temple that
my wish could be granted.
So I...
My wish is...
Setsu...
Now that the war is over, why don't we
go back to our original world together?
I actually found a way to go back.
Go back? Why?
Huh?
This stupid war is finally over.
There's still so much more
to see in this place.
This is finally the start of our
happy-go-lucky life in another world.
Why?
Why would Setsu say that to me?
Do you feel despair because
your vow was not kept?
Do you feel envy because he
does not see things as you do?
Well, best of luck with your life back home.
See ya, Toma.
No, Setsu!
No... You can't leave me again...
You promised me...
It has to be me by your side!
Do you feel despair toward this world?
Setsu, I get it now.
I'll destroy everything that gets in the way.
Humans, demons, Beastmen...
I'll kill them all!
Then you'll go back to the way you were, right?
Hey... Toma?
Yes! Setsu, you have to pay
attention to me and only me!
If someone else is going to take
you from me, I might as well...
Glutton!
Toma?!
Yes, excellent!
That's my Setsu!
Toma! Snap out of it!
You're the one who should
snap out of it, Setsu!
Setsu-sama?
Who are they?
Oh, they must be the ones who tricked you.
I don't understand a word you're saying!
People who get in my way, people who
seduce Setsu... are all unnecessary.
This world doesn't need anyone
other than Setsu and me!
Toma!
Setsu!
Setsu-sama!
Ouch...
Hey, none of my wishes came true.
I'm so tired now.
I guess I was alone to the very end.
What is this?
Hey, get walking!
Starting today's experiments now.
Magic power levels are rising.
This is dangerous for us.
Data collection is our first priority.
Understood.
As expected, magic organ transplants between
sisters do not trigger a rejection reaction.
Let's transplant the other one immediately.
No! No more experiments!
Someone help me!
Let me out! Let me out of here!
I will escape this place, I swear!
I will, I will, I will...
There is no place for us
to live in this world.
No... No!
No more! No, no, no!
If we're not allowed to live or die
in this world, we might as well...
Oh, so there were others like me after all.
Sure, I'll save you.
What?! What's going on?!
We're being attacked from above!
The building won't hold!
It's collapsing?!
Let us out! Open these doors, you shitbags!
No! I can't take this!
There. Now you're all free.
Won't you join me?
I want to destroy this world full of despair.
Destroy...
...this world?
You should come, too.
We are the same, rejected by this world.
I'm glad you're well, Setsu.
I'll finally win you over this time.
Thanks for waiting, guys.
My wounds have completely healed.
So, are you ready?
Let's become gods together,
as this world reaches its end.
Data viitoare
Ajungând pentru a doua oară pe câmpul de luptă
Next time:
"Arriving at a Battlefield for a Second Time."